{
  "1": {
	"Question": "What year did the flood occur?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "1513 BCE",
	  "607 BCE"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "2370 BCE",
	"Refernece": "https://www.jw.org/finder?wtlocale=E&docid=1200001150&srctype=wol&srcid=share&par=2"
  },
  "2": {
	"Question": "What was the prophet Daniel's Babylonian name?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Fred",
	  "Shadrach",
	  "Nebuchadnezzar"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Belteshazzar",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200001117#h=5"
  },
  "3": {
	"Question": "How big was Noah's ark?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "800 sq ft",
	  "big as the titanic"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "300 cubits long, 50 cubits wide, and 30 cubits high",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "4": {
	"Question": "What year did the Bible Students change their names to Jehovah's Witnesses?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "1935",
	  "1914"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "1931",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "5": {
	"Question": "Which one of Jesus's apostles saw a vision of unclean animals and was told to 'slaughter and eat' them?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Paul",
	  "James"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Peter",
	"Refernece": "Acts 10:11-13"
  },
  "6": {
	"Question": "What was the first kind of bird that Noah released from the ark to check if the waters had receded?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Dove",
	  "Ostrich"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Raven",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "7": {
	"Question": "How many stones did David select to prepare in fighting Goliath?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "6",
	  "7"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "5",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "8": {
	"Question": "Who replaced Judas after his betrayal?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Paul",
	  "Timothy"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Matthias",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1102009043?q=judas+replaced&p=par"
  },
  "9": {
	"Question": "Who baptized Jesus?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "He baptised himself",
	  "Joseph"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "John the Baptist",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "10": {
	"Question": "In Nehemiah's time, how many days did it take to complete the rebuilding of the walls of Jererusalem?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "14",
	  "49",
	  "157"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "52",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200003212#h=12"
  },
  "11": {
	"Question": "Who was the apostle Andrew's brother?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "James",
	  "Bartholomew"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Peter",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000273#h=3"
  },
  "12": {
	"Question": "What year was Aaron born?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "1513 BCE",
	  "607 BCE",
	  "2370 BCE"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "1597 BCE",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000005#h=3"
  },
  "13": {
	"Question": "Meaning \"senseless\" or \"stupid\", what was the name of Abigail's husband before she was married to King David?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Nebuchadnezzar",
	  "Korah",
	  "Achan"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Nabal",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000037#h=3"
  },
  "14": {
	"Question": "How old was Abram when he was given the name Abraham?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "53",
	  "33",
	  "77"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "99",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000060"
  },
  "15": {
	"Question": "Shem and Abraham's lives overlapped.",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": ["FALSE"],
	"Correct Answer": "TRUE",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000060#h=6"
  },
  "16": {
	"Question": "How old was Abram when he began to move to the land of Canaan?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "90",
	  "62",
	  "45"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "75",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000060#h=9"
  },
  "17": {
	"Question": "Which man's home did the Ark of the Covenant remain for 70 years before being transferred to Jerusalem?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "King David",
	  "Samuel",
	  "King Solomon"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Abinadab",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000046#h=4"
  },
  "18": {
	"Question": "When Achan took from the city of Jerico what \"[belonged] to Jehovah\" (Joshua 6:17), what items did he not take?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "A garment from Shinar",
	  "50-shekel gold bar",
	  "200 silver shekels"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "An acacia wood table",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000074#h=4"
  },
  "19": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Acts?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Paul",
	  "Matthew"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Luke",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000084"
  },
  "20": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Judges?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Sampson",
	  "David",
	  "Moses"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Samuel",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "21": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Ruth?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Ruth",
	  "Nehemiah",
	  "Solomon"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Samuel",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "22": {
	"Question": "Who wrote 1 Kings and 2 Kings?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "David",
	  "Solomon",
	  "Samuel"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Jeremiah",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "23": {
	"Question": "Who wrote 1 Chronicles and 2 Chronicles?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Moses",
	  "David",
	  "Paul"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Ezra",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "24": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Esther?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Esther",
	  "Moses",
	  "Ezra"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Mordecai",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "25": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Ecclesiastes?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "David",
	  "Paul",
	  "Jeremiah"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Solomon",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "26": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Lamentations?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Solomon",
	  "David",
	  "Samuel"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Jeremiah",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "27": {
	"Question": "Who wrote the Bible book of Revelation?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Peter",
	  "Matthew",
	  "Mark"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "John",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "28": {
	"Question": "What location was the Ark of the Covenant kept in the temple?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "On the roof",
	  "In the inner courtyard",
	  "Between the pillars"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Most Holy",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "29": {
	"Question": "Who was Jacob's son Asher's mother?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Rachel",
	  "Leah"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Zilpah",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "30": {
	"Question": "In ancient Israel, what was a the nearest male relative called who was under obligation to atone for one who had been killed?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Mr. Revenge",
	  "Avenger of Life",
	  "Redeemer of Blood"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Avenger of Blood",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000473"
  },
  "31": {
	"Question": "What is the name of Jacob's 12th son?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Joseph",
	  "Asher",
	  "Judah"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Benjamin",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "32": {
	"Question": "What is the name of Jacob's firstborn son?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Naphtali",
	  "Dan",
	  "Joseph"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Reuben",
	"Refernece": null
  },
  "33": {
	"Question": "Only three Roman Caesars who were ruling during the period covered by the Christian Greek Scriptures were mentioned by name. Which name is not included among them?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Augustus",
	  "Tiberius",
	  "Claudius"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Caligula",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000852"
  },
  "34": {
	"Question": "How many days did the 12 spies that Moses sent out preview the land?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "150",
	  "14",
	  "30"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "40",
	"Refernece": "https://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200000863"
  },
  "35": {
	"Question": "The statue of what type of angel was put on top of the Ark of the Covenant?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Archangel",
	  "Seraph"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Cherub",
	"Refernece": "https://www.jw.org/finder?srcid=jwlshare&wtlocale=E&prefer=lang&docid=1200000945"
  },
  "36": {
	"Question": "What Bible name means worthless and senseless?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Enoch",
	  "Judas",
	  "Achan"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Nabal",
	"Refernece": "1 Samuel 25:25"
  },
  "37": {
	"Question": "Who was the 1st non-Jew to have Holy Spirit fall upon him?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Silas",
	  "Timothy"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Cornelius",
	"Refernece": "Acts 10:44,45\nhttps://wol.jw.org/en/wol/d/r1/lp-e/1200001041?q=Cornelius&p=par#h=4"
  },
  "38": {
	"Question": "Which political ruler did Jehovah have an angel strike down with worms so that he died?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Tiberius Caesar",
	  "Nebuchadnezzar"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Harod Agrippa",
	"Refernece": "Acts 12:23"
  },
  "39": {
	"Question": "Who lived for 969 years?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Adam",
	  "Noah"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Methuselah",
	"Refernece": "Genesis 5:27"
  },
  "40": {
	"Question": "What animal did Jesus liken King Herod to and why?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Donkey because of his stubbornness",
	  "Lion since he was a King"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Fox because of his craftiness",
	"Refernece": "Luke 13:32"
  },
  "41": {
	"Question": "How many years did Jehovah strike Nebuchadnezzar with insanity?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Six",
	  "Ten",
	  "Two"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Seven",
	"Refernece": "Daniel 4:32"
  },
  "42": {
	"Question": "Which profit did Jehovah have walk around naked and barefoot?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Moses",
	  "Jeremiah",
	  "Elisha"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Isaiah",
	"Refernece": "Isaiah 20:3"
  },
  "43": {
	"Question": "What insect did John the baptizer eat along with honey?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Ants",
	  "Bees"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Locusts",
	"Refernece": "Mathew 3:4"
  },
  "44": {
	"Question": "How many silver coins did Judas Iscariot receive for betraying Jesus?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "42",
	  "100",
	  "2"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "30",
	"Refernece": "Mathew 26:15"
  },
  "45": {
	"Question": "What kind of bird brought food to the profit Elijah?",
	"Other Multiple Choice Answers": [
	  "Ostriches",
	  "Chickens",
	  "Finches"
	],
	"Correct Answer": "Ravens",
	"Refernece": "1 Kings 17:6"
  }
}
